In this lesson I want to talk with you about course or payment plans.
I structured all the information in one presentation that you can easy follow it.
Of course, we'll have some resources which goes to the course of the documentation about payment plans,
about some models, usages, and some rate limits.
So you can find always the actual information because, of course, in the future,
the information can be up to date and price might be changed.
So you can always find the actual information on the course sort of website.
But this presentation will give you a quick overview of payment plans that you'll explain
when better to use switch plans, what features they provide, and so we can easily compare them.
The good news you can start using the course sort of for free,
but with some monthly limits on completions and chart interactions.
But it will be enough to check if it's a right choice for you or not.
And if you want some more extensive usage, you can choose one of the payment plans.
So the first plan is course of free or they call it also hotbee plan.
They provide you two thousand top completions per month.
A top completions is when you start typing your code.
I could sort of suggest you some changes or some code you can use.
The risk in other features is agents.
They limit some requests, they not tell how much exactly they limit this request,
but they are limited to comparing to paid models, paid, paid plans.
You can use really a lot of models.
Compare it to comparing to a compiler. All models are available even in free plan,
but of course with some limitations.
So some more advanced models will have some limits
and you won't be able to use them too often.
For example, they suggest you to use the anthropic models, the cloud,
hikers, the cloud sonnets, the cloud opos.
You see all the latest models are available.
You can also use CHIGPT-4.4 mini 4.1.
Also there is access for AGPT-4.5 previews in U.S. version and the other versions.
You can also use Google game mini flash and pro 2.5 version.
You can have access to a grok from XAI.
And you can, of course, have access to the deep thick.
It has access to V3 and V3.1 models also.
It has access for reasoning model, R1.
I just not mentioned it here, but you can use any model you want,
but just on some free models without limits and the rest of the models with limits.
You can also use prop one.
If you use your first installation of course or you have it for two weeks
so you can use more advanced models with bigger limits.
Let's talk about next plan course or pro.
It's recommended for most of the users because if you are developer,
you need to do a lot of top completions, a lot of agenda requests,
you need to have a limited request.
It cost about 20 bucks per month,
but if you want to pay on the early basis, it's of course a bit cheaper.
Comparison 2, hip hop capacity, not suggest free version for students, teachers,
and open source maintainers, unfortunately.
If not about the top completions, you have unlimited top completions
and same for agents, but it's only for free models.
And for some more expensive models, rate you have the rate limits.
You can check what are rate limits on your website.
Also you have the access for all models as free plan,
and you will have access for some more advanced features.
You can have access for max mode if you enable it.
If you request your prompts, you will have more power,
so I think it will have more bigger context,
and the access system will use more resources to transfer
to your prompt more accurately and more faster.
You can use also some background agents.
Some automated workflows, you can set up,
and like, even if you're not at the computer,
so they can be executed.
Of course, you can have access for some bug board,
some EICod review for merge requests.
If you're talking about,
if it's, this limit is not enough for you,
but the next one, ultra, is too expensive for you,
because it costs 200 dollars per month.
It's not mentioned on the main page,
but if you follow the link from the resources,
I attach to this lesson.
You will find, in the other commentations, this plan as well.
You will have three EIC limits for more expensive models,
and it will cost 60 dollars per month.
So this is the main difference.
If you talk about the COSOR Ultra,
it has two times bigger limits for more expensive models,
but of course cost also more expensive.
It's recommended for most advanced AI users,
who really make a lot of requests.
If you talk about them,
they have team plan.
It costs 40 dollars per month,
and you can play on the early basis.
Of course, it will be cheaper in 40 dollar per month per seat,
per user.
You have unlimited top completion, same as in problem,
you have unlimited agent requests for free models,
and they additionally give you 500 premium model agent request.
So it's really nice.
You can use some other features like some privacy mode.
You can also read more about it on the documentation.
You can have a name does work with users' touch of your team.
You can have some centralized team building,
some SSO feature for easier authorization and more safety,
and also access to pure indexing.
If you have bigger enterprise for your company,
you can use enterprise plan.
They don't say the price how it costs,
but I think they can make it configurable,
depending on how much people you have,
how much resources you go to need, and etc.
So you can just chat them, or send them mail,
and they will do some suggestion for you.
You can still use all available models,
but you have some additional features like seat management,
some access control features, and some priority support,
and account management.
It's now more about usage pricing.
The limits included in individual and team subscriptions,
sufficient for most users,
but if you reach your limits for agent model,
you can always purchase additional usage at APIs rates,
for individual plans like Pro, Pro Plus, and Ultra,
APIs, it's cost per tokens per request,
so you can check it also into documentation.
If you have your team plan,
so you can do some additional request for the support,
so they will give you some additional options, I think.
About marks more types per unit,
it will give you more power to make in your API request.
I hope it was useful for you and see you in the next lesson.